so five of you all together yeah this is all of us and there are two other members in my group
that's a total of nine where do you plan to find the rest huh we're gonna need 15 total right
we can use fill-ins for the other players we'll just recruit players who want to return to the
real world but can't we won't be able to rely on them but they won't care about getting any cards
either which means that winning the contest will be entirely up to the nine of us so do we have a
chance how strong are our opponents they're tough but if we can't manage to get eight wins we can
switch members and try again so whether we can beat them depends on you guys we're gonna want to
see your wren first when we do we'll decide if we need you
dear to me
See you!
Wow.
I see the tables have turned, haven't they?
Well, so be it.
Here I go.
Whoa, awesome.
I can jump even higher at full strength.
My personal bet so far is 16 meters, 80 centimeters.
Ready, go!
Huh?
They broke my personal record without even trying.
How much did they improve in such a short amount of time?
That's very impressive.
Though, I could still go quite a bit higher myself.
Hey, how about we go again?
No way.
You won't want to stop until you win.
One more!
Just one more time!
And you passed, by the way.
That was a nice jump.
Sorry about that.
Just kids.
Let it slide, okay?
We believe you guys are strong.
But we're gonna be playing sports, so we're going to have to decide who will compete in which one.
Fine, but do we have any idea what sports they'll be selecting?
We managed to confirm these eight.
Depending on our success, we should all be ready for the possibility that they'll want to add more to the list.
I understand.
Hey!
This is bad!
Hmm?
What is it?
Team Genthrou is up to 97 cards.
That means that they're only missing...
Strip of Beach.
And Wild Luck Alexandrite.
Over the past week, we've simulated contingencies and prepared accordingly.
Given Team Genthrou's situation, defeat isn't the luxury we can afford.
We're gonna win this!
Yes, we certainly are!
This isn't so bad.
Right, let's go!
Let's start off with some boxing.
I'm about to send you packing.
His special abilities teleportation.
We already know that he's able to teleport his uppercut.
Fight!
So, damn, he's fast.
He's an infighter?
Closing the gap takes away an emitter's advantage.
He'll be so busy blocking, he won't have the chance to teleport.
Awesome!
The pattern inscribed on the ring is called Divine Script, and it augments Nen.
In other words, he can only teleport while standing inside the ring.
Essentially, he's advertising that he isn't nearly as strong as he'd like us to believe.
He's not worth our time.
The winner is Barry!
We did it!
The winner is Odriot!
The winner is Kes!
Ha-ha!
Ha!
All right!
That's three wins!
In terms of combat, those six are incredibly strong.
This is getting interesting.
If you want, you guys can throw your matches.
I can handle it from here.
Roger that.
Hold on!
Huh?
I'm done following your stupid orders!
I'll be doing things my own way from now on!
Alright, Brad! Let's step outside!
Outside, huh? Wait, don't you mean the Sumo ring?
I'm done messing around! Want me to kill you right here and now?
Hey, Bopo-Bo, stop!
That violates our agreement. You wanna go back to jail, Bopo-Bo?
I don't give a damn! I'm all done playing this game together!
Are you right here and now?
Hey! Bo-Bo-Bo, stop!
That violates our agreement.
You wanna go back to jail, Bo-Bo-Bo?
I don't give a damn!
I'm all done playing this ridiculous game!
Come on, you guys, who's with me?
If we team up, we can totally crush that damn bastard!
Then we can find a boat and use it to get off this damn island!
Breaking the taboo warrants severe punishment.
Or did I not tell him that?
Yeah, you sure did.
Did that idiot think I wouldn't kill him?
Well, I suppose I'll go next.
Hey, this looks bad!
There's no way we can fight those guys!
Hang on, we'll be the only ones doing the fighting.
We explained all of this.
If the nine of us can't secure eight victories,
you're all welcome to forfeit.
None of you guys have to fight them.
You're positive?
You guarantee we won't have to fight?
Yes, so don't worry.
That guy has a significantly stronger aura than anyone else.
And judging by that conversation,
I'm almost certain he's a game master.
I have a question.
Since that guy is dead now,
what happens to the sumo match?
Hmm?
Oh, you can have the win.
Okay, but we never actually decided who we were gonna have compete.
You already told everyone you were going to do the sumo!
I don't care who you give the win to.
So just give it to one of the guys who's standing in the back.
Then, I guess, you win sumo.
Me? Uh, okay.
That gives us four wins.
Now that that's settled, I think I'll go with an eight-on-eight game.
A dodgeball.
Pick eight members for your team.
As you can see, I already have mine.
Wait!
How is this going to be scored?
It's one point per person, right?
Yes, one point each.
Eight points will go to whichever team is victorious.
Simple enough?
So that's how this works.
No matter how many of his weaker members we defeat,
he can still win the entire game by himself.
Razor and his 14 devils.
So the 14 devils is his Nen ability.
Look, I'm against this!
If we have to field eight, then you need two more players!
You're crazy if you think I'm gonna fight that guy!
Uh, me too!
I'm getting out of here!
Once the match starts, you can let yourself get hit on purpose and-
Don't give me that crap!
You guys saw what happened!
If he hits us with that ball, we're dead meat!
Oh, so that we're perfectly clear.
We'll be using a normal ball.
But, Nen will make it as strong as the projectile I launched earlier.
This is crazy!
I'm leaving!
He's right!
No game is worth dying over!
Wait, don't decide now!
Give us a second to think of something!
Damn!
We only have six players of any use.
So we're forced to pick the remaining two from these spineless wimps.
Let's do this by ourselves!
If we're risking our lives here, we need willing players.
Do you mind if we only field six people?
Yeah, afraid I can't let you do that.
Both teams need eight members on the field, there's no getting around it.
Otherwise, why would we have you recruit fifteen people?
No point arguing with an in-game character.
But wasn't Bopabo your friend?
I don't get it.
What could he have done that was so bad he deserved to die for it?
Robbery, rape, and murder too.
Eleven confirmed counts if you want to get specific.
This is happening in the real world.
This isn't a virtual world.
Greed Island really exists.
This game takes place in the world we all know.
However, revealing that information to a player who truly believes that they're inside a game is taboo.
So that's why Bopabo was executed.
This guy here, Razor, he's a game master. A real human.
Game master?
It means he's one of the people who made this game.
Wait, but then...
Bopabo and the other pirates are probably condemned inmates.
He disobeyed orders and attempted to instigate a mutiny.
Execution was warranted.
This is real? It's not fake?
No, it is not fake.
I never realized that.
I had never even considered it.
Well, it really doesn't matter much in the long run.
Since this island is still isolated from the rest of the world.
Hey, wait a second.
If this is real life, then does that mean that Gene is here too?
On Greed Island?
Gene?
I see.
Huh?
You're going freaks, I presume.
Yeah.
Your dad told me that you would be coming here someday.
And not to take it easy on you.
Hey, I've had enough of this. I'm not ready to die yet.
Kill me out! I'm getting out of here!
No!
Wait, stop!
It's fine. Let them go.
But then we can't have a match.
We still can if I count as three.
You're doing the same thing, right? So it's not a problem.
No, that's fine.
Looks like we have an eight-on-eight game.
Here are the rules.
Each team starts with seven players on the court and one out.
First team with no players in the court loses.
Any player who's hit with a ball while in the court is out and goes outside.
However, you may bring one player inside the court again by saying back.
Also, if the ball lands outside the court and you don't have any players there, the opposing team gets the ball.
Now, the important stuff.
We'll use the cushion rule. Ricochets are alive until they land.
For example, if I throw the ball and it hits opposing player A, ricochets, and hits opposing player B before hitting the floor, both A and B are out.
But in that scenario, if player B can catch the ball, then player A is safe.
Exactly.
But let's say that I throw the ball and it hits opposing player A, ricochets, and hits my own teammate, player C, before hitting the floor.
Only player C is out, not A.
Let me get this straight.
So if player C catches the ball, does that mean player A is out?
That's right.
Any questions?
If an outside player hits somebody, are they out?
Yes, naturally.
Oh, but now that you mention it, only one player can return to the court using back.
I'm number zero, the ref. It's nice to meet you.
And now, we will begin the match.
Ready?
Go!
Go ahead, you take the first shot.
You sound pretty confident.
Well, consider this my way of saying hello!
You nailed him!
All right.
One down already.
Nice!
Let's just try to keep it up.
Okay!
That's two down!
Wow!
This is easy!
Well, whenever you're ready.
Huh?
Wait, what did you just say?
Oh, all I was saying is that we're ready to defeat you now.
Funny.
Very funny.
Go ahead and try!
Die!
He stopped it with one hand.
Time for us to launch the counter-attack.
He's so far back.
Is he gonna pass it?
So fast!
Can I dodge it?
No!
Will I survive if I catch it?
I'm dead!
Why, Garenu!
Hey, real nice rebound.
He's outside of the court.
Oh, I see.
You have the ability to change places with your Nenbe.
Dad?
That's not mad.
To have suprema'mne, how is the West Dark's Tiger game?
Will I dodge it?
No!
Will I do a great job?
Alright.
The Nen creature was completely shattered. That must reflect what Gorenu imagined would happen when he saw Razor's attack.
He instantly saw the gap between our opponent's strength and his own. He won't easily rid himself of that image, and it'll be impossible for him to recover in time.
He's finished, no question.
So Gorenu's Nen beast is the one that's out, right?
Right. The switch was performed with Nen, so it didn't break any rules. However, if you wish for Gorenu to return to the court, you'll have to use back.
Damn it. I can't let it end like this. Now, let's move on.
Their passing is so fast!
S-such speed! It's so fast, I can't follow the ball!
Hey, Tezgera! Behind you!
This thing is as heavy as a bowling ball. Not good. It must have insane power.
He focused his aura in his back. That's the only reason that wasn't a fatal blow. All right then, tend to his injuries.
No, I'm fine. Don't touch me.
Any player who becomes incapable of continuing the game is disqualified. They won't be allowed to play in or out of the court, so please keep that in mind.
Are you okay, boss? Yeah. But I can tell I'm really out of shape. Damn it! In overall combat ability, I should be stronger than those two by a long shot.
But in basics like agility and reflexes, I simply can't compete.
It's been quite a while since I've pushed myself. Maybe it's time to start my training over from scratch.
In fact, I don't think I've trained in the basics for several years now.
Ideally, we could knock out everybody on the other team without losing possession of the ball.
Hisoka!
Very well. Hand it over.
That's right. With his bungee gun, Hisoka can pull the ball back into his hand after every hit.
Now, let's have some fun, shall we? Surely this can't be all you've got.
Just bring it on.
Yes! That's three down, you guys! With back, they've still got five players.
We can stay on the offensive. All that's left is to decide which order to pick them off in.
Question, ref. What happens if the last player inside the court gets hit, but calls back at the same time?
That's not allowed. There would still be a moment when no players were on the court, so that team would lose.
But, if at the same time the last player was hit, someone else were to call back, that would be considered perfectly acceptable.
Perfectly acceptable.
Okay. Hisoka.
I see where this is going. We'll leave him for last.
He's got a strong serve. Numbers two, six, and seven couldn't catch it.
That's got some power to it.
If we're lucky, we can take out six and seven at the same time.
They... they merged!
You're a strong one.
Hey, is that even allowed?
It is.
If combining is okay, does that mean splitting is?
Yes, but you can't surpass the maximum number of players on the court.
All right.
Looks like it's my turn to attack.
Okay. We just have to get possession of the ball again.
If we're gonna stop him...
Ken!
Ah!
Their aura is smooth, almost beautiful.
They must have trained hard.
Even so, if Razor throws the ball at full strength, Ken won't be enough to save them.
They'll have to recover the ball knowing that they'll be injured.
I'm not convinced it's even possible.
So you boys know how to use Ken, huh?
Then you won't die.
That is, if you get really lucky, of course.
Here I come, goon.
Bring it!
No! Run! You'll die!
Kone!
Where's the ball?
Whoa!
It's launched all the way up there.
Gone! Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay, guys. Really.
Yeah, right.
I used Ko to guard my arms and head, but my legs just couldn't brace hard enough.
But next time...
I'm gonna catch it for sure!
And with that, Gone is fired up.
What kind of world is waiting for us to wait for the future?
The voice of the voice is the same way.
Now go like this.
Next time lies with harmful influences from us.
So let me get back to as long as soon as possible.
Because obviously completely lasts later...
Now go like this.
The voice of the voice of the voice is the same way.
Assay and연 pursued by Chris Houdler
riding on to the blowingIE
sometime Jegie
רétape
向かい風としていながら それでも進む理由がある
だから友よ 置いてくためだけに生きるのはまだ 早いだろ
身につけたもの 抱え込んだもの 手放したとき 始まる何か
上手く生きてく レシピを破り捨てて 感じるリズム そう僕らのやり方で
Coming up! The Great Island Tutorial!
I Don't Love with My Heart
My Heart
イラストの親友
キサウさん